<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Dota 2 Android App</string>
    <string name="activity_top_matches">Top Matches</string>
    <string name="activity_about">About</string>

    <string name="log_msg_debug">dota2androidapp.Debug</string>

    <string name="description_open_drawer">Open Menu</string>
    <string name="description_close_drawer">Close Menu</string>
    <string name="team_radiant">Radiant</string>
    <string name="team_dire">Dire</string>
    <string name="average_mmr">%d Avg. MMR</string>
    <string name="gold_advantage">+%1$d.%2$dk</string>
    <string name="elapsed_time">%1$d:%2$d</string>
    <string name="elapsed_time_corrected_sec">%1$d:0%2$d</string>
    <string name="spectate_command">Spectate command: watch_server %d</string>
    <string name="spectators">Spectators: %d</string>
    <string name="opendota">OpenDota</string>
    <string name="dotabuff">Dotabuff</string>
    <string name="info_top_matches">
        Overviews of top tournament and ranked matches currently being played and recently finished.
        Live matches are delayed just like in the Dota 2 spectator client.\n\n
        Tournament matches show the pro teams\' names instead of \"Radiant\" and \"Dire\". Live
        ranked matches are sorted by average MMR and pro players are highlighted with a distinct
        color. Recent matches are sorted by time finished (most recent at the top of the list).\n\n
        Swipe down to refresh the according list. Swipe left and right to switch between live and
        recent matches. Click once on a match to show or hide additional information. Press and hold
        on a ranked match to switch between pro players\' official names and current Steam
        names.\n\n
        To spectate a live match, find it in the \"Watch\" tab in your Dota 2 client. Alternatively,
        type the command below a live match into your Dota 2 console and press Enter.\n\n
        Click on the OpenDota or Dotabuff button below a recent match to view their specific match
        details in your browser.
    </string>
    <string name="paragraph_about0">
        This app is being developed and maintained by a small group of amateur and professional
        developers. We came together through a post on
        <a href="https://reddit.com/r/dota2/">/r/dota2</a>. You can follow the development and see
        the whole source code
        <a href="https://github.com/Rhacco/Dota2AndroidApp/">here</a>.
    </string>
    <string name="paragraph_about1">
        We started this app in the hopes of learning more about Android development. It has been
        quite a journey already and we are always looking to learn more by implementing new things.
    </string>
    <string name="paragraph_about2">
        The current state of the app is not the final result of this project. We are always looking
        for feedback, especially related to the UI. If you have any suggestions or bug reports,
        please let us know
        <a href="https://github.com/Rhacco/Dota2AndroidApp/issues">here</a>
        by creating a new issue.
    </string>
    <string name="dialog_ok">OK</string>
    <string name="error_permission_network_state">App needs permission to access the current network
        state!
    </string>
    <string name="error_permission_internet">App needs permission to connect to the internet!
    </string>
    <string name="error_no_internet">Network error. Please check your internet connection</string>
</resources>